[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Eric and Shellys cat in the film The Crow?", "correct_answer": "Gabriel", "incorrect_answers": ["Atilla", "Mystic", "Felix"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Solar System body was once considered a planet, but was later reclassified as a dwarf planet and a member of the Kuiper Belt.", "correct_answer": "Pluto", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Venus", "Jupiter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what African country was the 1950 movie The Black Rose mostly filmed?", "correct_answer": "Morocco", "incorrect_answers": ["Egypt", "Algeria", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This dormant volcano, which is 66 km northeast of Tehran, is the symbol of Iranian resistance against foreign rule.", "correct_answer": "Mount Damavand", "incorrect_answers": ["Mount Hood", "Krakatoa", "Krafla"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What nutrient essential for the human body does spinach contain in large quantities?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin A", "Iron", "Vitamin K"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What condition is characterised by an irrational fear of taking tests?", "correct_answer": "Testophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Placophobia", "Chronophobia", "Theologicophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is New York City the capital of New York?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about Madagascar?", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["It is slightly smaller than France.", "It is the worlds 56th-largest country in terms of area.", "It is the fifth largest island in the world."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mildred Pierce put Joan Crawfords name back up there in lights.  It was nominated for several Academy Awards.  Both Ann Blyth and Eve Arden were nominated for Best Supporting Actress.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the main purpose of pulleys?", "correct_answer": "They decrease the force needed to lift something.", "incorrect_answers": ["They are useless", "They halve the needed force", "They double the needed force"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actors made his debut at the age of 5 in a movie written and directed by his father?", "correct_answer": "Robert Downey, Jr.", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Duvall", "Robert Redford", "Robert De Niro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the Jacksons Chameleon?", "correct_answer": "It gives birth to 8-30 live young.", "incorrect_answers": ["It lays about 15-30 eggs that hatch in 10 days.", "It lays about 5-10 eggs that hatch immediately.", "It gives birth to 2-3 live young."]}]